ithinkapps.com 2018-01-05

# iThinkApps | mp3TrueEdit - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how C2 Solutions Limited (trading as www.ithinkapps.com) uses and protects any information that you give C2 Solutions Limited when you use this website.

C2 Solutions Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

C2 Solutions Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## A. What we collect

### 1\. Information collected by FastSpring (our online reseller for www.ithinkapps.com) 

The FastSpring online store collects personally identifiable information when you purchase our products from them. Every FastSpring order asks for personally identifiable information such as your name, contact information, and payment information. The use of the personally identifiable information collected by FastSpring is subject to FastSpring's Privacy Policy, which can be found at <http://www.fastspringstore.com/privacy.php>.

The FastSpring Online Store uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personally identifiable information is required. To make purchases from the FastSpring Online Store, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it's transmitted over the Internet.

### 2\. ﻿﻿﻿Information collected by Apple App Store (our online reseller for [www.ithinkapps.com](http://www.ithinkapps.com/))

We also offer our products through the Mac App Store. The Mac App Store is governed by Apple's privacy policy (<http://www.apple.com/privacy>). We receive no personal information from Apple when our products are purchased via the App Store.

### 3\. Information collected by other subcontractors and strategic partners.

C2 Solutions Limited may need to collect or process further information in order to perform essential business functions using other subcontractors and strategic partners who in-turn have compatible privacy policies.  
Currently one such partner is softWORKZ Innovation Inc. and their privacy policy on end user information can be found here: <http://www.softworkz.com/privacy/end_user_information.html>. 

### 4\. Information collected by our website

We may collect the following information when you complete our enquiry form:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

What we do with the information we gather:   
We use personally identifiable information collected by FastSpring to provide you with the license key information in case of accidental loss or deletion. In addition, this personally identifiable information is used to keep you posted on the latest releases or updates of our products.

Also, we require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may occasionally send a promotional e-mail about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. Should you decide that you no longer wish to receive any e-mail newsletters from us you can cancel at any time by following the instructions on the e-mail footer.

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

## B. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## C. How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies or alert you when a cookie is place on your computer, if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## D. Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## E. Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us, using our contact form or emailing us directly by clicking here.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us, use our contact form or by email us directly by clicking here.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
